♪Don't feel sad for the fallen flowers♪
♪ لا تشعر بالحزن على الزهور الحزينة ♪
♪Falling in the mortal world♪
♪ يتظاهر في العالم الفاني ♪
♪Keep all the memories♪
♪ استمر في جميع الذكريات ♪
♪Can't find any peace anymore♪
♪ لا يمكن العثور على أي سلام بعد الآن ♪
♪The storms can't kill my passion♪
♪ العواصف لا يمكن أن تقتل حمايتي ♪
♪But I need to endure♪
♪ لكنني بحاجة إلى تحمل ♪
♪Be serious even though I'm naive♪
♪ كن جادا على الرغم من أنني ساذجة ♪
♪If this is the destined fate♪
♪ إذا كان هذا هو القدر المقدر ♪
♪Even if I'll be hurt♪
حتى ولو تأذيت ♪
♪I'll protect the people♪
♪ سأحمي الناس ♪
♪The mountains sun and moon can be my witnesses♪
♪ الجبال الشمس والقمر يمكن أن يكون شاهداي ♪
♪Full of passion♪
♪ مليء بالحماقة ♪
♪Deep love and hatred♪
♪ الحب والكراهية العميق ♪
♪Melts in my heart along with the snow♪
♪ يذوب في قلبي مع الثلج ♪
=Royal Rumours=
= الشائعات الملكية =
=Episode 6=
= الحلقة 6 =
The decorations here
الزهور هنا
are different from anywhere else.
مختلفة من أي مكان آخر
Interesting.
مثير للاهتمام
(Why isn't he leaving yet?)
(لماذا لم يغادر بعد؟)
(How would I know?)
(كيف أعرف؟)
(Ask him.)
(أسأله)
(I asked several times.)
(سألت عدة مرات)
(He still won't leave.)
(ما زال لن يغادر)
(What can I do?)
(ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل؟)
(Aren't you worried people will say)
(ألا تشعر بالقلق من أن الناس سيقولون)
(that Prince Ying and Princess Hua have grown so close)
(أن الأمير ينغ والأميرة هوا نمت بشكل وثيق جدا
(after staying in the same room together?)
(بعد البقاء في الغرفة نفسها؟) نفس الغرفة معا؟
(Don't jinx it.)
(لا تجلب معها)
Prince Ying.
الأمير ينغ
Yes?
نعم
It's already noon.
إنه وقت الظهر بالفعل
Isn't it time...
ألم يحن الوقت
Is it time for lunch?
هل حان وقت الغداء
I didn't expect you
لم أكن أتوقع منك
to be so hospitable.
أن تكوني مضيافة جدا
Then I shall
إذن سأقبل
accept your invitation.
سأقبل دعوتك
He even wants to eat here.
حتى إنه يريد أن يأكل هنا
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو
Watch your steps.
انتبه لخطواتك
Don't fall.
لا تسقط
I heard that my brother is dining here.
سمعت أن أخي يأكل هنا
I shall join them.
وسأنضم إليهم
Your Highness.
صاحبة السمو
Liuli.
ليولي
You don't mind, right?
أنت لا تمانع، أليس كذلك؟
I thought you would at least
اعتقدت أنك على الأقل
reflect on yourself
أن تفكر في نفسك
after the plum blossom banquet.
بعد مأدبة زهر البرقوق
I didn't expect you
لم أكن أتوقع منك
to come here so soon.
أن تأتي إلى هنا في هذا الوقت القريب
I've been whipped a few times
لقد تم جلدي بضع مرات
by mother.
حسب الأم
The plum blossom banquet
مأدبة زهر البرقوق
has frightened Princess Hua.
ويفزع الأميرة هوا
Don't worry, Princess Hua.
لا تقلق يا أميرة هوا
I will treat you well.
سأعاملك بشكل جيد
I won't let you suffer any more harm.
لن أسمح لك أن تعاني من أي ضرر آخر
Who was it at the banquet
من كان في المأدبة
that frightened Princess Hua?
هذه الأميرة المخيفة هوا؟
It was mother.
كانت أمي
If it's her fault,
إذا كان خطأها
can you just ignore it?
هل يمكنك تجاهله فحسب؟
I didn't.
لم أفعل
I'm here to make amends.
أنا هنا للتعويض
As long as Princess Hua
طالما الأميرة هوا
stays with me all the time,
تبقى معي طوال الوقت
day and night,
نهارا وليلا
she will be safe.
ستكون آمنة
(Hua Mansion)
(قصر هوا)
It's become more challenging.
أصبح أكثر تحديا
There are actually two princes
هناك أميران في الحقيقة
in Hua Liuli's mansion.
في قصر هوا ليولي
We can take them down in one go.
يمكننا إنزالهم في جولة واحدة
Then we will have
إذن سنحصل
the State of Jin under our control.
دولة جين تحت سيطرتنا
Don't you know how many traps there are
ألا تعرف كم الفخاخ هناك
in the mansion?
في القصة؟
Take them all down?
انزلها جميعا؟
I think
أعتقد
we are the ones in trouble.
نحن الذين في ورطة
Didn't Hua Liuli say
ألم تقل هوا ليولي
she would continue
كانت ستواصل
to deal with us?
للتعامل معنا؟
Is she
هل هي
planning to conspire with us
التي تخطط للتآمر معنا
to assassinate that...
لاغتيال ذلك...
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Conspire with you
التآمر معك
to assassinate herself?
لاغتيال نفسها؟
- She did it.
- لقد فعلت ذلك
I can't believe that even my poison
لا أصدّق أنه حتى سمي
couldn't kill her.
لا يمكن أن يقتلها
Forget it.
انس الأمر
Let's get our act together
دعنا نتصرف معا
and wait for the right time.
وننتظر الوقت المناسب
Great.
عظيم
I can finally live longer.
يمكنني أخيرًا أن أعيش لفترة أطول
Yes.
نعم
You know
أنت تعرف
what Jinling Garden looks like
يبدو حديقة جين لينغ
without ever going out.
دون الخروج أبدا
You've even brought
لقد أحضرت
the chief manservant along.
الخادم الرئيسي هنا
Your Highness.
صاحبة السمو
I may be from the border,
قد أكون من الحدود
but I'm not ignorant of
لكنني لا أجهل
things in the capital.
في العاصمة
You, on the other hand,
من ناحية أخرى
must have frequented Jinling Garden.
لا بد أنهم ارتددوا حديقة جينلينغ
I'm hungry.
أنا جائعة
What you see before you
ما تراه أمامك
is the daily food
هو الطعام اليومي
of the local people at the border.
للسكان المحليين على الحدود
They are all very delicious.
جميعهم لذيذة جدا
What's this?
ما هذا؟
This is pork offal.
هذا فضالة لحم الخنزير
And what is this?
وما هذا؟
Why does it smell rotten?
لماذا تفوح مني رائحة؟
This is milk curd.
هذا لعنة الحليب
Is it not available here?
أليست متوفرة هنا؟
I'm from a desolate land
أنا من أرض معتدلة
and my family
و عائلتي
is poor.
فقيرة
So
لذلك
I can only
لا يمكنني إلا
offer this
أن يعرض هذا
to both of you.
لكليكما
I hope
آمل
you don't mind.
لا تمانع
Princess Hua.
الأميرة هوا
Don't you have water here?
ألا لديك الماء هنا؟
You can drink
يمكنك أن تشربي
the pork offal soup
حساء فرسان الخنزير
in front of you.
أمامها
If you don't like it,
إذا كنت لا تحب ذلك
you can try the milk curd.
يمكنك تجربة لعنة الحليب
Brother, please.
أخي، من فضلك
Your Highness, please.
صاحب السمو، من فضلك
After you.
بعد أنت
I should let you go first.
يجب أن أدعك تذهبين أولا
What's in that little porcelain bottle?
ما قصة زجاجة الخزف الصغيرة تلك؟
This is the vegetable juice I made.
هذه هي عصير الخضار الذي صنعته
After all, there are many vegetables grown here.
بعد كل شيء، هناك العديد الخضروات المزروعة هنا
I will drink this first.
سأشرب هذا أولا
I like vegetable juice.
أحب عصير الخضار
It smells good.
رائحته جيدة
Let me taste it first.
دعني أتذوقها أولا
Prince Ying.
الأمير ينغ
Is it bad?
هل هو سيء؟
It's good.
إنه لذيذ
I like it.
يعجبني هذا
I'm already full.
أنا متخمة بالفعل
Thank you for the meal.
شكرًا على الوجبة
I shall take my leave.
سأغادر الآن
I'll take my leave first.
سأغادر أولا
Since my brother is not staying,
نظرا لأن أخي لا يقيم
then I shall leave, too.
إذن سأغادر أنا أيضًا
Take good care of your body.
اعتني بجسدك جيدا
Miss.
الآنسة
They've finally left.
لقد غادرا أخيرا
I want to be a feeble woman,
أريد أن أكون امرأة ضعيفة
but I don't really want
لكنني لا أريد حقًا
to be sick.
أن أكون مريضة
Your Highness.
سموك
What brings you here all of a sudden?
ما الذي جاء بك إلى هنا فجأة؟
Father intends
الأب يعتزم
to betroth Princess Hua to me.
إلى خطبة الأميرة هوا لي
It's not appropriate for you to come.
ليس من المناسب لك أن تأتي
I heard that father was furious
سمعت أن الأب كان غاضبا
when he found out that Princess Hua
عندما اكتشف أن الأميرة هوا
had been poisoned at the banquet.
تم تسميتها في المأدبة
It seems that
يبدو أن
the betrothal will be put aside.
سوف يتم تجاهل الخطوبة
Father never said so.
الأب لم يقل ذلك أبدا
It will happen.
سيحدث هذا
Besides, Princess Hua
إلى جانب ذلك، الأميرة هوا
has already grown fond of me.
قد نمت بالفعل أحباء مني
She invited me to lunch.
دعتني إلى الغداء
Your Highness.
صاحبة السمو
You should avoid suspicion.
يجب أن تتجنبي الشك
Really?
حقًا؟
That won't do.
هذا لن ينفع
Father entrusted me to find
أبي عهد إليّ للعثور
the assassin.
القاتل
Not only do I have to handle the case,
ليس فقط عليّ أن أتعامل مع القضية
I also have to protect Princess Hua.
يجب أن أحمي الأميرة هوا أيضا
You, on the other hand,
أنت، من الناحية الأخرى
it's still uncertain
لا يزال غير مؤكد
whether Consort Xian
ما إذا كان القرينة شيان
can be
يمكن أن تكون
cleared off the case.
خارج القضية
You are the one who needs to avoid suspicion.
أنت الشخص الذي يحتاج إلى تجنب الشك
Miss, eat something.
الآنسة، كلي شيئا
You are starving.
أنت تتضور جوعًا
My head hurts.
رأسي يؤلمني
I lost my appetite.
فقدت شهيتي
Miss.
الآنسة
Why is Prince Ying
لماذا الأمير ينغ
so confident?
واثقا جدا؟
He is the Emperor's first son.
إنه الابن الأول للإمبراطور
Besides, Consort Xian
إلى جانب ذلك، القرينة شيان
dotes on him so much.
يحمله كثيرًا
It's normal that he's so confident.
من الطبيعي أن يكون واثقًا من نفسه كثيرًا
The only thing is that the Crown Prince
الشيء الوحيد هو أن ولي عهد
started hiding things for me
شرع في إخفاء الأشياء لي
at the plum blossom banquet,
في مأدبة زهر البرقوق
which I don't quite get.
التي لا أحصل عليها تماما
Maybe
ربما
he suddenly found out that you are a good person
اكتشف فجأة أنك أنت فتاة صالحة
and didn't pick on us.
ولم تأخذ منا
Do you really think so?
هل تعتقد ذلك حقا؟
Maybe he has ulterior motives.
ربما لديه دوافع خفية
No one knows what he's thinking.
لا أحد يعرف ما يفكر به
Anyway, we need
على أي حال، نحن بحاجة
to be more careful.
أن نكون أكثر حذرا
I still have to be wary of him.
لا يزال يتعين علي أن أكون حذرا منه
(Jinling Garden)
(حديقة جين لينغ)
(Hua Mansion, Western Suburb)
(طائفة هوا، الضاحية الغربية)
(Hua Liuli)
(هوا ليولي)
(Ji Yuansu)
(جي يوانسو)
I don't know
لا أعرف
what you're up to,
ما الذي تقوم به
but I don't think
لكنني لا أعتقد أنك
you're a sinister person.
أنت شخص شنيع
If the assassins
إذا كان القاتل
were really from Jinpo,
كانوا حقا من جينبو
would that prove that
هل سيثبت ذلك
there was no connection between
لا توجد علاقة
Princess Hua and Jinpo?
الأميرة هوا وجينبو؟
It's complicated
إنه معقد
as it is a one-sided story.
لأنها قصة من طرف واحد
It is uncertain yet.
لم تُعرف بعد
If you really think
إذا كنت تفكر حقا
that Princess Hua
أن الأميرة هوا
is not such a sinister person,
ليست امرأة شريرة
why don't you get to know her in a different approach?
لماذا لا تعرفها في نهج مختلف؟
I can change my approach
يمكنني تغيير نهجي
to know her,
لمعرفتها
but what do you do?
ولكن ماذا تفعل؟
As one of you men,
كواحد منكم
I should address your concerns.
يجب أن أتناول مخاوفك
I will continue to pursue
سأواصل السعي
the hidden truth about Princess Hua.
الحقيقة المخفية بشأن الأميرة هوا
If you think there's nothing wrong
إذا كنت تعتقد أنه لا شيء خاطئ
with Princess Hua,
مع الأميرة هوا
don't you blame me
ألا تلومني
for the wrong intelligence
على المعلومات الاستخباراتية الخطأ
I gave you in the first place?
لقد أعطيتك في المقام الأول؟
Why should I?
لم عليّ فعل ذلك؟
Everything that reaches my ears
كل ما يصل إلى أذني
comes from a wide
يأتي من مصادر متنوعة
variety of sources.
طائفة من المصادر
Occasional mistakes are unavoidable.
لا مفر من وقوع أخطاء عرضية
Besides, this matter
بالإضافة إلى ذلك، هذه المسألة
is not yet settled.
لم تتم تسويتها بعد
Don't worry about it.
لا تقلق بشأن ذلك
A different approach?
نهج مختلف؟
Don't underestimate the youngest daughter of the Hua family
لا تقلل من شأن الأصغر ابنة عائلة هوا
and the Crown Prince.
وولي عهد
Let the assassins of Jinpo
دع قتلة جينبو
go on their way
اذهب في طريقهم
so that we can position
حتى نتمكن من الموقع
our men more securely.
رجالنا أكثر أمنا
What do you mean?
ماذا تعني؟
If the youngest daughter of the Hua family is really sick,
إذا كانت الابنة الأصغر عائلة هوا مريضة حقا
why has she escaped harm so many times?
لماذا هربت ضرر مرات عديدة؟
If the Crown Prince is really a brutal man,
إذا كان ولي عهد رجلا وحشيا حقا
why did His Majesty
لماذا جلالة الإمبراطور
grant him the throne?
منحه العرش؟
(He's squinting his eyes.)
(إنه يبدد عينيه)
(What is he up to again?)
(ما الذي يريد فعله مجددًا؟)
(She's staring at me.)
(إنها تحدق بي)
(What is she up to again?)
(ما الذي تفعله مرة أخرى؟)
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو
Where are you
أين أنت
taking me today?
تأخذني اليوم؟
You'll know when you get there.
ستعرفين عندما تصلين إلى هناك
Didn't His Majesty
ألم يكن جلالة الملك
ask you to investigate
طلب منك التحقيق
the case?
القضية؟
I'm flattered
شكرا لكم
that you're spending
أنك تنفق
so much time on me.
الكثير من الوقت علي
If the assassins
إذا كان القاتل
were targeting you,
كانوا يستهدفون
wouldn't your presence beside me
ألا يكون حضورك إلى جانبي
be their perfect goal?
يكون هدفهم المثالي؟
Then there's no need
لا داعي لذلك
for me to look elsewhere.
أن أنظر إلى مكان آخر
You got the point.
لقد فهمت النقطة
Your Highness, we are here.
صاحب السمو، نحن هنا
Your Highness.
صاحبة السمو
You may get down first.
يمكنك الهبوط أولا
I am not in good health.
أنا ليست في صحة جيدة
I will take some time.
سآخذ بعض الوقت
Be quick.
كن سريعا
(Wrestling Arena)
(معركة أرينا)
Princess Hua.
الأميرة هوا
My father used to
كان والدي
bring me here when I was a child.
أحضرني إلى هنا عندما كنت طفلة
Have you ever
هل سبق لك أن فعلت
seen anything like this?
رأيت أي شيء من هذا القبيل؟
They are fighting.
إنهم يقاتلون
So barbaric.
وحشية جدا
Princess Shun'an
الأميرة شون آن
has always admired General Wei's talent.
لطالما كانت معجبة بموهبة الجنرال وي
After General Wei went to the border,
بعد أن ذهب الجنرال وي إلى الحدود
Princess Shun'an regularly
عقدت الأميرة شون ران بانتظام
held wrestling competitions.
نظمت مسابقات في المصارعة
No wonder Princess Shun'an
لا عجب أن الأميرة شون آن
treats me so well.
يعاملني بشكل جيد
By the way,
بالمناسبة
do you have the same skills
هل لديك نفس المهارات
as General Wei in wrestling?
مثل الجنرال وي في المصارعة؟
I am not in good health.
أنا لست في صحة جيدة
I can't overdo myself.
لا يمكنني المبالغة في ذلك
Well, that's a shame.
حسنًا، هذا مؤسف
Bravo. Fight!
شجاع!
Everyone.
الجميع
The fight between General Hua
القتال بين الجنرال هوا
and General Wei
والجنرال وي
is now
تم تذكره الآن
remembered by many
تذكره الكثيرون
as a heroic fight.
كمعركة بطولية
Today,
اليوم
I have invited
لقد وجهت الدعوة
Princess Hua,
الأميرة هوا
the daughter of the Protector General,
ابنة الحامي العام
Marquis Chang'an,
ماركيز تشانغ آن
- to be the judge for this match. - (He's testing me again.)
- أن يكون القاضي لهذه المباراة - (إنه يختبرني مجددًا)
Let's give her a warm welcome.
دعنا نرحب بها بحرارة
(Just don't expose my martial arts.)
(فقط لا فضح فنون الدفاع عن النفس)
No.
لا
What's wrong?
ما الخطب؟
Stop it.
توقف
Princess Hua is weak.
الأميرة هوا ضعيفة
How could you bring her
كيف يمكنك إحضارها
to such a dangerous place?
إلى هذا المكان الخطير؟
I'm just asking her
أنا فقط أطلب منها
to be a judge
أن تصبح قاضية
and just stand
يقف فقط
comfortably on the stage.
بشكل مريح على المسرح
No way.
لا يمكن
That's dangerous, too.
هذا خطير أيضًا
It's not.
ليس كذلك
How can there be no danger
كيف لا يكون هناك خطر
When the wrestlers get into a fight,
عندما يدخل المصارعة في قتال
they couldn't care less about
لا يهتمون أقل
the people around them.
الأشخاص من حولهم
What if Princess Hua can't avoid it
ماذا لو لم تتمكن الأميرة هوا من تجنب ذلك
and gets hurt?
وتتأذى؟
Princess Hua.
الأميرة هوا
I believe
أعتقد
that a person who has been brought up in the Hua family
أن الشخص الذي نشب في عائلة هوا
is bold and resolute
جريئة وحاسمة
regardless of their physical condition.
بغض النظر عن حالتهم البدنية
If you
إذا كنت
can't even be a judge,
لا يمكن حتى أن تكون قاضيا
I'm afraid people will be disappointed
أخشى أن يشعر الناس بخيبة الأمل
in the two generals.
في الجنرالين
(He keeps)
(إنه يحتفظ)
(bringing up my parents.)
(تربية والديّ)
(He's so cruel.)
(إنه قاس جدًا)
(It seems he won't)
(يبدو أنه لن يكون)
(let me slide today.)
(دعني أنزلق اليوم)
In that case,
في هذه الحالة
I will
سأقوم
take on this task.
لهذه المهمة
However,
لكن
I am in poor health.
أنا في صحة سيئة
So...
لذلك
Let's begin.
دعنا نبدأ
Princess Hua, be careful.
الأميرة هوا، كن حذرا
Great!
عظيم!
May I know your names?
هل لي أن أعرف اسمك؟
Our names...
اسمنا...
Are not worth mentioning.
لا تستحق الذكر
Start.
ابدأ
Princess Hua.
الأميرة هوا
Be careful, Princess Hua.
كن حذرا، الأميرة هوا
Why do those two wrestlers
لماذا يصارع هذان المصارعة
keep approaching
تقترب
Hua Liuli?
هوا ليولي؟
- Isn't this bullying? - Hey.
- أليس هذا التنمر؟ - اسمعي
His Highness is so mean.
سموه لئيم جدا
Why is he torturing Hua Liuli like this?
لماذا يعذّب هوا ليولي هكذا؟
Torture?
التعذيب؟
His Highness is doing
سموه يفعل ذلك
the right thing.
عن المناسب
Goodness.
يا إلهي
Help.
النجدة
Be careful, guys.
كن حذرًا يا رفاق
Did you see it?
هل رأيتم ذلك؟
I think Hua Liuli
أعتقد أن هوا ليولي
threw a kick just now.
ركل أركل للتو
Really?
حقًا؟
But I didn't
لكنني لم أر
see it clearly.
رؤيته بوضوح
Hua Liuli
هوا ليولي
is definitely not an ordinary person.
بالتأكيد ليس شخصا عاديا
Princess Hua.
الأميرة هوا
Princess Hua, be careful.
الأميرة هوا، كن حذرا
Help.
لمساعدتي
Princess Hua.
الأميرة هوا
No.
لا
Stop now!
توقف الآن!
Help.
النجدة
Princess Hua.
الأميرة هوا
- Princess Hua. - Prince Ying.
- الأميرة هوا - الأمير ينغ
Be careful.
كن حذرا
Princess Hua.
الأميرة هوا
Princess Hua, be careful.
الأميرة هوا، كن حذرا
(Since you are merciless,)
(بما أنك بلا رحمة،)
(don't blame me for being unrighteous.)
(لا تلوميني على أنني غير صالح)
(What's going on?)
"ماذا يجري؟"
(Good luck.)
(حظًا موفقًا)
His Highness.
صاحب السمو
Your Highness.
سموك
I am sorry.
أنا آسف
Forgive me.
سامحني
Your Highness, are you all right?
صاحب السمو، هل أنت بخير؟
Princess Hua.
الأميرة هوا
You are quite skilled.
أنت ماهرة جدا
(Memorial) It's all about you.
(نصب تذكاري) كل شيء عنك
Father.
أبي
I'm just
أنا فقط
doing the right thing.
القيام بالشيء الصحيح
Is that why
هو هذا السبب
you always spend time
دائما تقضي الوقت
at Princess Hua's place?
في مكان الأميرة هوا؟
Of course.
بالطبع
Princess Hua was almost assassinated
الأميرة هوا كادت أن تغادر
at Consort Xian's plum blossom banquet.
في مأدبة زهر البرقوق للقرينة شيان
I am protecting her.
أنا أحميها
Still, it's not appropriate
مع ذلك، ليس من المناسب
for you to take Princess Hua
بالنسبة لك لأخذ الأميرة هوا
to a horse racing track
إلى مسار سباقات الحصان
and a wrestling arena.
وساحة للمصارعة
I'm responsible for her reception.
أنا مسؤول عن استقبالها
I found her homesick.
وجدتها متشابكة
So I took her to the racetrack
لذلك أخذتها إلى المسار
to get over it.
للسيطرة عليه
Is it wrong?
هل من خطأ؟
I've heard that
لقد سمعت أن
the wrestlers
المصارعة
even attacked Princess Hua.
حتى هاجموا الأميرة هوا
I wonder
أتساءل
what your explanation is
ما هو توضيحك
for this?
لهذا؟
I'm the one who got hurt.
أنا من تأذيت
Do you care for me?
هل تهتم بأمري؟
I have my own arrangements
لدي ترتيباتي الخاصة
for the investigation.
للتحقيق
Do I need to report to you all?
هل أحتاج إلى تقديم تقرير لكم جميعا؟
Have you made any progress
هل أحرزت أي تقدم
with that case?
في هذه الحالة؟
Yes.
نعم
The assassins at the banquet and before
القاتل في المأدبة وقبلها
were from Jinpo.
كانوا من جينبو
Junior Secretary Pei
السكرتير الأول بي
has drawn up the official document.
قام بإعداد الوثيقة الرسمية
This...
هذا...
Impossible.
مستحيل
Jinpo soldiers are the most reserved.
جنود جينبو هم الأكثر تحفظا
How did you get them to talk?
كيف أجبرتهم على التحدث؟
Kill.
اقتل
I'll beat you to death.
سأضربك حتى الموت
They killed another one.
قتلوا واحدة أخرى
It's been several days.
مر عدة أيام
This cell is almost empty.
هذه الزنزانة فارغة تقريبا
The State of Jin
دولة جين
is too scary.
مخيف جدا
Master Pei.
سيد بي
Good job.
أحسنت صنعًا
Give him extra meal tonight.
أعطيه وجبة إضافية الليلة
- Yes. - Thank you.
- نعم - شكرًا لك
- Take him away.
- خذوه بعيدا
Move.
ابتعدي
My Lord.
سيدي
We are not at fault, My Lord.
نحن لسنا مخطئين يا سيدي
Please don't kill us.
أرجوك لا تقتلنا
Jihuai.
جيهواي
How many are left?
كم تبقى؟
Your Highness.
سموك
All that's left
كل ما تبقى
are these little thieves.
هم هؤلاء اللصوص الصغار
What were the charges against them?
ما هي التهم الموجهة إليهم؟
Why hadn't they been executed?
لماذا لم يتم إعدامهم؟
I can't remember exactly.
لا أستطيع أن أتذكر بالضبط
With so many cases in Supreme Court,
والكثير من القضايا في المحكمة العليا
who knows what these two little thieves
من يعرف ما هذين اللصوص الصغار
have done?
قد فعلت؟
I will see
سأرى
what the new cases are.
ما هي القضايا الجديدة
Unsolvable cases
القضايا غير القابلة للحل
will be blamed on
سيتم لومي
the people of Jinpo.
على الرغم من ذلك
Antique shop burglary.
سطو على متجر التحف
Dozens of forgeries were stolen.
سُرقت عشرات المزروعات
Jinpo's people did it.
قام شعب جينبو بذلك
Falling into a sty while stealing a pig.
وقعت في لذيذة بينما سرقت خنزير
Chased by a dog for miles
تطارده كلبة لأميال
and the dog got lost and didn't go home.
فقدت الكلب ولم تعد إلى المنزل
Jinpo's people did it.
فعل سكان جينبو ذلك
Robbing a woman.
سلب امرأة
Found out it was a man
اكتشف أنه رجل
and got beaten up.
وضرب
Jinpo's people did it.
شعب جينبو فعل ذلك
(Robbery of a woman)
(نهب امرأة)
Jinpo.
جينبو
Don't you dare
إياك أن تجرؤ
accuse our Jinpo!
نتهم جينبو!
We are not that bad.
نحن لسنا بهذا السوء
- Don't you dare
- ألا تجرؤ
- accuse our Jinpo!
- تتهم جينبو! - اتهمنا بـ جينبو!
Yours?
لك؟
Jihuai.
جيهواي
Yes.
نعم
Jot it down.
امضغي
These two have
هذان الاثنان قد أبلغانا
informed us of the secrets of Jinpo.
أبلغتنا بأسرار جينبو
Spread the word to Jinpo
أرسل الكلمة إلى جينبو
and see how Jinpo
لمعرفة كيف لـ جينبو
will treat their families.
سوف يعاملون عائلاتهم
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو
You've slayed it.
لقد صفعتها
All the ministers were silent.
لزم جميع الوزراء الصمت
They're just a bunch of old codgers
إنهم مجرد حفنة من الخدم القدامى
who are easy to deal with.
الذين يسهل التعامل معهم
Unlike Princess Hua.
خلافا للأميرة هوا
Are you
هل أنت
trying to have a go
تحاول الحصول على الذهاب
at Princess Hua?
في الأميرة هوا؟
If the Hua family isn't so powerful,
إذا لم تكن عائلة هوا قوية جدا
why would I
لماذا لا
try so hard?
صعوبة بالغة؟
I can just kill them.
يمكنني فقط قتلهم
Well,
إذن
you have wronged.
لقد ظلمت
You're right.
أنت على حق
I feel wronged extremely.
أشعر بالظلم الشديد
However,
لكن
I can still suffer from it.
لا يزال بإمكاني المعاناة منه
What do you mean?
ماذا تعني؟
How about a heart-to-heart chat?
ما رأيك بمذبحة القلب؟
Then you really
إذن أنت حقا
have to suffer from it.
يجب أن تعاني منه
(Minister Mansion)
(قصر الوزير)
Jiamin.
جيامين
Jiamin?
جيامين؟
Ouch.
هذا مؤلم
Gently, mother.
أمي
Look at you.
انظري لنفسك
(Account Book) Spending money lavishly.
(كتاب الحسابات) إنفاق المال بغزارة
What a disgrace.
يا لها من عار
Can't you
ألا يمكنك
be like Hua Liuli?
مثل هوا ليولي؟
(Account Book)
(كتاب الحسابات)
I heard that the dress
سمعت أن الفستان
she wore to the plum blossom banquet
ارتدت إلى مأدبة زهر البرقوق
was made from our scraps.
مصنوعة من خرطوشات
Mother.
أمي
Can you stop mentioning Hua Liuli?
هل يمكنك التوقف عن ذكر هوا ليولي؟
I really hate her.
أنا أكرهها حقا
What has she done to you?
ماذا فعلت بك؟
I was once the first noble daughter of the capital.
كنت ذات مرة نبيلة الأولى ابنة العاصمة
Everyone knows that
الجميع يعلم أنني
I was to be betrothed to the Prince.
كان يجب أن أكون خطيبا إلى الأمير
And now
والآن
here she is,
ها هي ذا
stealing all the limelight from me
سرقة كل الليلة مني
and His Majesty is giving her a betrothal.
وصاحب الجلالة هو إعطائها خطبة
Except for the Third Prince,
باستثناء الأمير الثالث
the Crown Prince and Prince Ying
ولي عهد والأمير ينغ
are all around her.
جميعهم من حولها
Of course I'm annoyed.
بالطبع أنا منزعجة
Didn't you say you didn't want
ألم تقل إنك لا تريد
to marry a prince before?
للزواج من أمير من قبل؟
You were obsessed with
كنت مهووس بها
Yun Han from Jinling Garden.
يون هان من حديقة جين لينغ
Why did you change your mind?
لماذا غيّرت رأيك؟
Idolising Yun Han
مهزلة يون هان
is not the same as getting married.
ليس مثل الزواج
They were supposed to be mine
كان من المفترض أن يكونوا لي
and now they've all been taken away.
والآن تم اقتيادهم جميعا
I'm not happy.
أنا لست سعيدةً
You're not happy.
أنت لست سعيدًا
So you stay home all day?
إذًا أنت تبقى في المنزل طوال اليوم؟
Learn from your mother.
اتعلم من أمك
When I adored
عندما أخطأت
General Wei,
الجنرال وي
I went
ذهبت
wherever she went.
أينما ذهبت
She is not a man.
إنها ليست رجلا
If she were,
إذا كانت كذلك
she'd have been on my palms.
كانت ستكون على يدي
Are you sure?
هل أنت متأكدة؟
Of course.
بالطبع
Why else would General Wei
لماذا قد يكون الجنرال وي
have entrusted me with
عهد إلي
such an important task
مهمة هامة كهذه
as a wrestling competition?
كمباراة مصارعة؟
Don't listen to Consort Xian and the others
لا تصغي إلى قرينة شيان والآخرين
about how close they are to her.
عن مدى قربهم منها
In fact, General Wei's
في الواقع، الجنرال وي
real best friend
أفضل صديق حقيقي
is me.
هو أنا
So do you like Hua Liuli?
هل تحب هوا ليولي؟
Don't say yes.
لا تقل نعم
She is General Wei's daughter.
إنها ابنة الجنرال وي
Of course I like her.
بالطبع أحبها
Fine.
حسنا
I don't like her.
لا أحبها
You are the best.
أنت الأفضل
I just want to tell you that
أريد أن أخبرك أنه
you have to go for what you like.
عليك أن تذهبي لقاء ما تحبين
You must not lose.
يجب ألا تخسر
Leave.
غادر
- Get out. - Remember to tell Liuli
- اخرج - تذكر أن تخبر ليولي
to come over when she's free.
أن تأتي عندما تكون متفرغة
Mother, get out.
أمي، اخرجي
(Ten Rules of Noble Women) Men are defined by their strength
(القواعد العشرة للمرأة الحزينة) يتم تعريف الرجال وفقا لقوتهم
and women by their gentleness.
والنساء برأيهن
A strong man is noble,
الرجل القوي نبيل
a gentle woman is beautiful.
امرأة لطيفة جميلة
If my mother had seen this,
إذا كانت أمي قد رأيت هذا
she would have burned it all down.
كانت ستحرقه جميعا
Miss.
الآنسة
Your priority right now
أولويتك الآن
should be His Highness
يجب أن يكون سموه
who almost
الذي كاد
got knocked unconscious
وقع فاقد للوعي
to protect you.
لحمايتك
Yes.
نعم
Oh, no.
لا
He is the Crown Prince.
إنه ولي عهد
How could you jump on him?
كيف يمكنك القفز عليه؟
Don't make a fuss.
لا تثيري جلبة
I am a delicate girl.
أنا فتاة حساسة
Are you expecting me
هل تنتظر مني
to protect him?
لحمايته؟
He is the Crown Prince.
إنه ولي عهد
Exactly.
بالضبط
I want him to know
أريده أن يعرف
how unlucky he is to meet me
كم هو غير محظوظ لمقابلتي
so he won't want to
حتى لا يريد
bother me all the time.
أن يزعجني طوال الوقت
However,
لكن
I think
أعتقد
I've discovered
لقد اكتشفت
His Highness's weakness.
ضعف سموه
(His Highness is)
(الأمير هو)
(a man who shows compassion for women.)
(رجل يظهر الرحمة تجاه المرأة)
Could it be...
هل يمكن أن يكون...
Your Highness.
سموك
What brings you here?
ما الذي جاء بك إلى هنا؟
Miss.
الآنسة
He really came today.
لقد جاء حقا اليوم
It seems that the trick
يبدو أن الحيل
doesn't work on him.
لا يعمل معه
Oh, no.
لا
He must have come for revenge.
لا بد أنه جاء للانتقام
I need to hide.
أحتاج إلى الاختباء
Greetings, Your Highness.
تحياتي يا صاحب السمو
Your Highness.
سموك
You are a true man.
أنت رجل حقيقي
I'm really impressed with
أنا معجبة حقا
the speed of your recovery.
سرعة تعافيك
Impressed.
معجب
Your Highness.
سموك
You
أنت
look good today.
تبدين جميلة اليوم
Father thought
اعتقد الأب
I acted too abruptly the other day
تصرفت بشكل مفاجئ في ذلك اليوم
and asked me to come and apologise to you.
وطلبت مني أن آتي والاعتذار لك
After deep reflection,
بعد التفكير العميق
I think father was right.
أعتقد أن الأب كان على حق
So I've decided
لذلك قررت
to take you to
أن آخذك
the most suitable place
المكان الأنسب
as compensation.
كتعويض
Don't move.
لا تتحركوا
Your Highness.
سموك
You can take it out on me.
يمكنك أن تأخذها علي
Don't hurt her.
لا تؤذيها
Miss, run.
الآنسة، اركض
Princess Hua.
الأميرة هوا
Is your maidservant
هل خادمتك
not in her right mind?
ليست في عقلها الصحيح؟
It's crooked.
انها مائلة
Though Consort Xian
على الرغم من أن القرينة شيان
had hosted a plum blossom banquet,
قد استضافت مأدبة زهر البرقوق
I thought
اعتقدت
you might not have enjoyed it.
ربما لم تستمتعا به
So
لذلك
I...
أنا...
(I vomited a lot of blood)
(لقد انتظرت الكثير من الدم)
(and you still bring me here)
(وما زلت تحضر لي إلى هنا)
(to recall it.)
(للتذكر)
(Do you hate me so much?)
(هل تكرهني كثيرًا؟)
(I really can't grasp his mind.)
(لا أستطيع حقا فهم رأيه)
Princess Hua.
الأميرة هوا
I'd like to ask you.
أود أن أطلب منك
At the plum blossom banquet...
في مأدبة زهر البرقوق
Princess Hua.
الأميرة هوا
Thank you, Your Highness.
شكرا لك يا صاحب السمو
(Gosh.)
(يا إلهي)
(He's starting to suspect me again.)
"بدأ يشكك بي مجددًا"
(There you are.)
(ها أنت ذا)
(I mustn't talk foolishly today.)
(يجب ألا أتحدث سخيفا اليوم)
(Take a deep breath.)
(خذي نفسا عميقا)
Prince Ying.
الأمير ينغ
What a coincidence.
يا لها من مصادفة
You are here, too.
أنت هنا أيضًا
What brings you here?
ما الذي جاء بك إلى هنا؟
Prince Ying.
الأمير ينغ
Are you not happy to see me?
ألست سعيدا لرؤيتي؟
Last time you said to my face
قلت في المرة الماضية عن وجهي
that I was unattractive.
أنني كنت غير جذاب
Then why should I smile
إذن لماذا يجب أن أبتسم
when I see you?
عندما أراك؟
No.
لا
Prince Ying.
الأمير ينغ
Actually, I was...
في الواقع، كنت...
Forget it.
انس الأمر
I've thought about it.
فكرت في الأمر
If you don't think I look good,
إن لم تظن أنني أبدو جميلة
that means you don't have an aesthetic.
هذا يعني أنه ليس لديك جمال
You have bad taste.
ذوقك سيء
Yes.
نعم
You are right.
أنت على حق
So let me
لذلك دعني
take a good look at you
ألقي نظرة جيدة عليك
to improve my aesthetic sense.
لتحسين حسي الجمالي
I am generous.
أنا كريمة
Of course I will
بالطبع سأعطيك
give you a chance.
أعطيك فرصة
Go ahead.
هيا
Princess.
الأميرة
Have you seen enough?
هل رأيت ما يكفي؟
I shall take my leave.
سأغادر الآن
Prince Ying
الأمير ينغ
is really as eye-catching
هو حقا ملعب للعجب
as Yun Han.
مثل يون هان
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو
Did you ask me out today
هل طلبت مني الخروج اليوم
just to watch flowers?
لمشاهدة الزهور فحسب؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Aren't they pretty?
أليست جميلة؟
Master Pei.
سيد بي
Do you think His Highness
هل تعتقد أن سموه
is having a heart-to-heart chat?
هو تناول محادثة من القلب؟
What do you think he is doing?
ماذا رأيك يفعل؟
Pretty.
جميلة
Talking about flowers.
تتحدث عن الأزهار
Now this is a real deal.
الآن هذه صفقة حقيقية
Let's go.
لنذهب
(Looks like he's trying to trick me again.)
(يبدو أنه يحاول أن يخدعني مرة أخرى) للخدعة مرة أخرى)
Princess Hua.
الأميرة هوا
The flowers are dazzling.
الأزهار مذهلة
Wipe your eyes.
امحو عينيك
Thank you, Your Highness.
شكرا لك يا صاحب السمو
(This handkerchief...)
(هذا المنديل...)
Princess Hua.
الأميرة هوا
Liuli.
ليولي
What do you see?
ماذا ترى؟
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو
Where did you
أين وجدت
find this handkerchief?
العثور على هذا المنديل؟
In fact,
في الواقع
I have many questions
لدي الكثير من الأسئلة
for you since then.
لك منذ ذلك الحين
Why does the blood on this handkerchief
لماذا الدم على هذا منديل
smell like fruit?
أشم مثل الفاكهة؟
I've always wanted to have
لقد أردت دائما أن أتناول
a good chat with you.
محادثة جيدة معك
You don't have to
ليس عليك
be so secretive
أن تكوني سرية جدا
in front of me.
أمامي
(Do you think)
(هل تعتقد)
(this will make me submit?)
(هذا سيجعلني أخضع؟)
(You)
(أنت)
(underestimate me.)
(تقلل من شأني)
Princess Hua.
الأميرة هوا
What do you think?
ما رأيك
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو
I'm not going to lie,
لن أكذب
but this fruity fragrance
ولكن هذا العطر الفائق
is actually my body scent.
هو رائحة جسدي
If you don't believe me,
إذا كنت لا تصدقني
you can smell it.
يمكنك شم رائحته
No.
لا
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I thought you didn't believe me.
ظننت أنك لا تصدّقني
Then I shall let you
إذن سأدعك
smell the fruity scent.
أشم رائحة الفاكهة
(Goodness.)
(يا إلهي)
(You usually act tough.)
(عادة ما تتصرف بصرامة)
(Why are you blushing?)
(لماذا تحمرّين؟)
(No one will believe it.)
(لا أحد يصدق ذلك)
It's getting late.
إن الوقت متأخر
I am a little tired.
أنا متعب قليلًا
I'll take my leave.
سأغادر أولا
Princess Hua.
الأميرة هوا
(She...)
(هي...)
(She's actually...)
(إنها في الحقيقة...)
(He doesn't think I am)
(إنه لا يعتقد أنني كذلك)
(doing it on purpose, does he?)
(القيام بذلك عن قصد، أليس كذلك؟)
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Yuanhao.
يوانهاو
Why are you here again?
لماذا أنت هنا مرة أخرى؟
You haven't even
لم تفكري حتى
explained what you're doing
شرحت ما تفعلين
and you're questioning me?
وأنت تشكك فيّ؟
Princess Hua.
الأميرة هوا
Do you still remember
هل ما زلت تتذكر
our engagement?
خطبتنا؟
I think
أعتقد
there is such a thing.
هناك شيء كهذا
Even though she's not my wife now,
رغم أنها ليست زوجتي الآن
she will be.
فستكون كذلك
Well,
إذن
since that is the case,
ونظرا لأن هذا هو الحال
I think your doing
أعتقد أن فعلك
is really inappropriate.
غير مناسب حقا
(Although Prince Ying is goofy,)
(على الرغم من أن الأمير ينغ مفخر،)
(he can help me out.)
(يمكنه مساعدتي)
Prince Ying.
الأمير ينغ
I think you are right.
أعتقد أنك على حق
His Majesty's order cannot be violated.
أمر جلالته لا يمكن أن ينتهك
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو
It's not really appropriate for you
ليس من المناسب لك حقا
to keep asking me out like this.
لمواصلة طلبي الخروج هكذا
I think
أعتقد
we should keep some distance.
يجب أن نحافظ على مسافة ما
I came to you
أنا جئت إليك
to work on the case
للعمل على القضية
and to protect you.
ولحمايتك
On the other hand,
من ناحية أخرى
don't you think
ألا تعتقد
you've acted
أنك تصرفت
inappropriately as well?
بشكل غير مناسب أيضا؟
I'm told
قيل
the case is now closed.
الحالة مغلقة الآن
So you don't need to
لذلك لست بحاجة إلى
waste any more time
أن تضيع المزيد من الوقت
on me.
عليّ
As for my safety,
أما بالنسبة لسلامتي
Prince Ying will protect me, too.
الأمير ينغ سيحميني أيضا
Of course.
بالطبع
Jingua.
جينغوا
Yes.
نعم
Get the carriage.
أحضر العربة
Princess Hua.
الأميرة هوا
Please.
تفضل
Thank you, Prince Ying.
شكرا لك يا أمير ينغ
(I called you here)
(اتصلت بك هنا)
(to tell you that)
(لإخبارك أن)
(I have no intention of making an enemy of you.)
(لا أنوي) خلق عدو لك)
(Ankang Garden) (How can I gain your trust?)
(حديقة أنكانغ) (كيف يمكنني كسب ثقتك؟)
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو
Guess what
خمن ما
I've got for you today.
لدي لك اليوم
Jiannan and Shaochun liquor.
خمور جيانان وشاوتشون
This liquor
هذا النبيذ
is rarely stocked
نادرا ما يتم تخزينها
in the liquor house.
في منزل الخمور
Get someone to fire up the stove.
اطلب شخصا ما لإطلاق النار من الموقد
We shall sit around the stove and heat the liquor
سنجلس حول الموقد ويقوم بتسخين الخمور
- while watching the moon. - Jihuai.
- أثناء مشاهدة القمر - جيهواي
Do you remember what you did
هل تتذكرين ما قمت به
last time you got drunk?
آخر مرة ثملت فيها؟
From today,
من اليوم
I refuse to drink around the stove.
أرفض أن أشرب حول الموقد
Here.
هنا
She actually said that
في الحقيقة
my eldest brother is better than me.
أخي الأكبر هو أفضل مني
What a joke.
يا لها من مزحة!
You were all groomed up.
جُهزت تمامًا
She is blind. Here.
إنها أعمى، هنا
I was trying to clear up any misunderstandings
كنت أحاول إزالة أي سوء تفاهم أي سوء تفاهم
with her today,
لديها اليوم
to make her less nervous
لجعلها أقل توترا
in front of me
أمامها الآن
and to be open with her,
وأن أكون منفتحة معها
but...
لكن...
It was too much for her.
كان الأمر أكثر من اللازم لها
This is unacceptable!
هذا غير مقبول!
Drink.
اشربي
So, Your highness,
يا إلهي!
what did you do?
ماذا فعلت؟
I just gave her back
أعدتها إلى هنا للتو
the handkerchief that
المنديل الذي
she spat blood on before.
التي تبصق دماء من قبل
I even gave her back the evidence.
حتى أنني أعادت لها الأدلة
I was sincere.
كنت صادقًا
Exactly.
بالضبط
She didn't appreciate it.
لم تكن تقدر ذلك
It was her problem.
كانت مشكلتها
Exactly.
بالضبط
Su.
سو
Listen.
اسمعوا
Let me share with you
دعني أشارك معك
a very good saying.
مقولة جيدة جدا
"Let go of your reservations
"التخلي عن تحفظاتك لتحقيق النتيجة المنشودة"
to achieve the desired result."
لتحقيق النتيجة المنشودة "
No way.
لا يمكن
Will it work?
هل سينجح الأمر؟
Yes.
نعم
(Pretentious Hour)
"لحظة التظاهر"
What a beautiful view.
يا لها من صورة جميلة
A plum blossom blooms in the cold, like a strip of white jade,
يزهر البرقوق في البرد مثل قطاع من اليشم الأبيض
away from the village road and close to the bridge over the stream.
بعيدا عن طريق القرية و قريب من الجسر فوق النهر
I didn't know it was the plum blossoms.
لم أكن أعلم أنها أزهار البرقوق
I thought it was the snow that hadn't melted.
اعتقدت أنه الثلج التي لم تكن قد ذاب
Prince Ying.
الأمير ينغ
You are so eloquent.
أنت بليغة جدا
In fact, this is
في الواقع، هذا هو
what my mother
ما طلبت مني أمي
told me to do.
أخبرتني أن أفعل
I just randomly recited it.
تذكرت ذلك بشكل عشوائي
You didn't understand anyway.
أنت لم تفهم على أي حال
Say it again.
كرر ما قلته
My mother was right.
كانت أمي محقة
You are hopeless.
أنت ميؤوس منك
I'll take my leave.
سأغادر
Wait.
انتظر
♪A new song is played by my fingers♪
♪ أغنية جديدة يعزفها أصابعي ♪
♪I can't talk or sleep under the moon♪
♪ لا أستطيع التحدث أو النوم تحت القمر ♪
♪I'm missing someone walking around the pavilion♪
♪ أفتقد شخصا ما أتجول حول الجناح ♪
♪I can hardly tell anyone♪
♪ لا أستطيع أن أقول لأي شخص ♪
♪Who will be in this mortal♪
♪ من سيكون في هذه الوفاة ♪
♪Know my heart and how I cry without showing anyone♪
♪ عرفت قلبي وأنت كيف أبكي دون إظهار أي شخص ♪
♪The memory has gone♪
♪ لقد اختفت الذاكرة ♪
♪Whose face is showing in my dream♪
♪ يظهر وجهي في حلمي ♪
♪How many times do I need to go through this♪
♪ كم مرة أحتاج إلى المرور بهذا ♪
♪Crying alone in front of the window♪
♪ الزواج وحده أمام النافذة ♪
♪Hearing the rain last night♪
♪ الاستماع إلى المطر ليلة أمس ♪
♪But my heart will not change♪
♪ لكن قلبي لن يتغير ♪
♪The clouds are being covered by the shadow of the moon♪
♪ الغيوم يتم تغطيتها في ظل القمر ♪
♪Who is rolling up the sleeve with the wind♪
♪ من يدمر النوم بالرياح ♪
♪Not worried about the grudges but for the ones not around♪
♪ لا تقلق بشأن الضغينة ولكن من لا حولها ♪
♪Telling my sorrowfulness in Fengyi Pavilion♪
♪ عزيمة في جناح فنغ يي ♪
♪But it's a shame a few autumns have passed♪
♪ لكنه من المؤسف لقد مرت بعض الأوهام ♪
♪It's hard to balance between the world and the one we love♪
♪ من الصعب التوازن بين العالم بين العالم الذي نحب ♪
♪The clouds are being covered by the shadow of the moon♪
♪ الغيوم يتم تغطيتها في ظل القمر ♪
♪I'm waiting while turning back♪
♪ أنا أنتظر بينما أعود ♪
♪I sighed as the old days are no longer here anymore♪
♪ شاهدت كالأيام الخوالي لم يعد هنا بعد الآن ♪
♪How many worries are there♪
♪ كم عدد الهموم هناك ♪
♪How many of us can grow old together♪
♪ كم الكثير منا يمكن أن يكبر في السن معا ♪
♪I wish you can have the world and the one you love♪
♪ أتمنى أن يكون لديك العالم العالم الذي تحبينه ♪